{
    "subject": "resource/Solo_(American_band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Solo (American band) is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9019589424133301,
            "question": "Where is the American band Solo from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.669908344745636,
            "question": "Is Solo a musical group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5545519590377808,
            "question": "What country is Solo from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3902476727962494,
            "question": "Are there any famous members of Solo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3688258230686188,
            "question": "How long has Solo been active as a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36836549639701843,
            "question": "What genre of music does Solo play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2915700376033783,
            "question": "Has Solo released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26842859387397766,
            "question": "What instruments do the members of Solo play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23867401480674744,
            "question": "Does Solo perform live concerts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20998549461364746,
            "question": "Where did Solo gain their initial popularity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Solo (American band) is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9004_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Solo perform live concerts?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9004_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments do the members of Solo play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9004_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Solo released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9004_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_166.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9004_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that Solo was formed when members traded their street singing on the boulevards of Los Angeles for a shot at conquering Amateur night at the Apollo in New York City, implying they are from the United States.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Solo\" is a group formed by American members and have performed and recorded albums in the U.S., thus supporting the statement that Solo is an American band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}